careersatsap.com 2017-07-13

# Careers | Privacy Statement | About SAP

**Skip to Content**

What describes your role best?

How would you rate the 2016 Integrated Report?

Excellent Very Good Good Fair Poor

How easily did you find the information you were looking for?

Very easy Easy Neutral Difficult Very difficult

  *     * English 
    * German 
    * Français 
    * Español 
    * 中文 
    * 日本 
  *     * 台灣 

English

### SAP Privacy Statement – Careers at SAP

**1\. Registration**  
By registering as a user on the website Careers at SAP, you voluntarily choose to provide SAP and any member of SAP Group with your personal data and you explicitly consent to the collection, processing and use of the information subject to the guidelines as described herein in the following.

You hereby acknowledge that SAP as a global Company operates joint administrative and cross-national by using multiple systems in order to share information about human resources for the purposes of a unified recruiting system. SAP may process the personal data manually or automatically by authorized employees of SAP and/or other authorized assigned third parties. SAP has internal policies that enable an equal security standard globally within SAP to comply with applicable data protection laws. Furthermore any assigned third party processing Your personal data on behalf of SAP, if the case may be, shall be obliged to maintain confidentiality and follow the same strict security measures of SAP.

Your personal data may be stored and processed by SAP to share it with any member of SAP Group worldwide within the scope of the recruiting purposes and for contacting You about job opportunity at SAP.

When You register as a user on the website Careers at SAP, SAP may record your IP address, name, surname, date of birth, address, telephone number or email-address and use cookies and other Internet technologies as referred to within the SAP Privacy Statement (http://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html) to gather general information about You.  
By registering as a user on the website Careers at SAP, You explicitly confirm that you are interested in an employment at SAP. You therefore voluntarily provide Your personal data to be used for recruiting purposes, in particular for filling and matching your profile with any and all open positions at SAP, including beyond those for which you specifically applied. The registration process is a default setting of the application process. If your application refers solely to one specific job opportunity then the process mentioned under Section 2 (Application) below applies.

By registering as a user on the website Careers at SAP and by releasing your profile, You furthermore agree to SAP contacting you for HR marketing purposes. If, at a specific time, you should no longer wish to be contacted especially for direct marketing or market research, we will respect your choice. Please use the following contact email: [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com). Furthermore SAP does not sell your personal data to third parties. If there is a job opportunity within SAP and it matches Your profile, SAP may forward your data to the responsible SAP managers within SAP Group for further validation and in order to contact You for interviews. The personal data will be processed in the form of databases and will be collected in secured personal files.

You may view and update your account and/or request correction, deletion or locking of your personal data at any time. Please refer to the email address mentioned within the SAP Privacy Statement or use the following “Contact email [mailto:careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)”.  
If you do not update your profile within a period of two years, SAP may send you an e-mail to ask you to update your profile. If you do not update your profile by the given deadline, your profile including your personal data will be deleted.  
Please use only private email addresses for requests. SAP will only send information to your private address.

**2\. Application**  
You also have the possibility to apply solely for one defined job opportunity. To activate these restrictions, You have to mark your user settings accordingly while activating Your registration or before sending Your application.

By applying for a specific job opportunity, You provide SAP with your personal data to the extent as mentioned above. You are responsible for ensuring that the personal data provided by You is correct and true. By submitting your application, You agree to your personal data being used in conjunction with the filling of open positions complying with Your profile by following the above mentioned principles unless stated otherwise below.

You have the option of withdrawing your application at any time. Your data will be deleted in accordance with the applicable laws once the application process ends or if you withdraw your application. However, your data will not be deleted for a certain time period if you released it for the registration process. In this case, the process described in Section 1 applies.

Please use only private addresses for requests. SAP will only send information to your private address.

**3\. Anonymous Surveys**  
The SAP HR Department continuously wants to improve their processes. Therefore, they will ask applicants (and former applicants with an active account) to participate in anonymous surveys once in a while. These surveys will either be conducted by SAP itself or by an specialized external processor on behalf of SAP. For this purpose any external processor will only get your name, e-mail address and a reference to an organizational unit within SAP. The surveys and the resulting reports will be completely anonymous. Your name and e-mail address will be deleted after our e-mail contact with you. Of course, it is completely up to you, whether you participate in such a survey. In case You prefer not to be contacted for surveys, please use the following mail: [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com).

If you have any questions or comments, please contact [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)

**4\. Use of Google Analytics**  
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

Additionally you can use this plugin: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en> Google has developed the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. It provides website visitors more choice on how their data is collected by Google Analytics, The add-on communicates with the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js) to indicate that information about the website visit should not be sent to Google Analytics.

### Datenschutzerklärung – Karriere

  **1\. Registrierung**

Mit der Registrierung auf der Website Careers at SAP stellen Sie SAP und allen Mitgliedern der SAP-Gruppe freiwillig Ihre persönlichen Daten zur Verfügung und willigen ausdrücklich in die Erfassung, Verarbeitung und Nutzung der Informationen gemäß den nachfolgend beschriebenen Richtlinien ein.

Sie erkennen hiermit an, dass SAP als globales Unternehmen in verschiedenen Ländern mit einer gemeinsamen Verwaltung agiert und unterschiedliche Systeme einsetzt, um Informationen für eine einheitliche Personalsuche auszutauschen. SAP kann die persönlichen Daten manuell oder automatisch durch berechtigte SAP-Mitarbeiter und/oder andere berechtigte Dritte verarbeiten. SAP verfügt über interne Richtlinien, die bei SAP weltweit den gleichen Sicherheitsstandard entsprechend den anwendbaren Datenschutzgesetzen gewährleisten. Außerdem ist jeder Dritte, der ggf. Ihre persönlichen Daten im Auftrag der SAP verarbeitet, verpflichtet, die Vertraulichkeit zu wahren und die gleichen strengen Sicherheitsmaßnahmen von SAP anzuwenden.

Ihre persönlichen Daten können von SAP gespeichert und verarbeitet sowie an Mitglieder der SAP-Gruppe weltweit im Rahmen der Personalsuche und zur Kontaktaufnahme bei offenen Positionen weitergegeben werden.

Bei der Registrierung auf der Website Careers at SAP kann SAP Ihre IP-Adresse, Vorname, Nachname, Geburtsdatum, Adresse, Telefonnummer oder E-Mail-Adresse erfassen und Cookies und andere Internettechnologien, wie in der SAP-Datenschutzerklärung (http://www.sap.com/corporate/de/legal/privacy.html) beschrieben, verwenden, um allgemeine Informationen über Sie zu sammeln.

Indem Sie sich auf der Website Careers at SAP registrieren, bekunden Sie explizit Ihr Interesse an einer Beschäftigung bei SAP. Sie stellen damit freiwillig Ihre persönlichen Daten über eine konkrete Bewerbung hinaus zum Zweck der Personalsuche zur Verfügung, vor allem damit Ihr Profil passenden offenen Stellen bei SAP zugeordnet werden kann. Die Registrierung ist die Standardeinstellung des Bewerbungsprozesses. Wenn Sie sich ausschließlich auf eine definierte Position bewerben möchten, gilt der unter Punkt 2 (Bewerbung) beschriebene Prozess.

Mit der Registrierung auf der Website Careers at SAP und der Freischaltung Ihres Profils erklären Sie sich außerdem damit einverstanden, dass SAP Sie im Rahmen von Personalmarketingmaßnahmen kontaktiert. Sollten Sie von einem bestimmten Zeitpunkt an nicht mehr wünschen, besonders im Rahmen des Direct Marketing und der Marktforschung kontaktiert zu werden, respektieren wir selbstverständlich Ihre Entscheidung. Bitte verwenden Sie zur Kontaktaufnahme die folgende E-Mail-Adresse: [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com). Außerdem verkauft SAP Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht an Dritte. Wenn eine auf Ihr Profil passende Stelle innerhalb von SAP angeboten wird, kann SAP Ihre Daten zur weiteren Prüfung auch an die verantwortlichen SAP-Manager innerhalb der SAP-Gruppe weitergeben, um Sie für ein Bewerbungsgespräch zu kontaktieren. Die persönlichen Daten werden in Form von Datenbanken verarbeitet und in gesicherten Personaldateien gesammelt.

Sie können jederzeit Ihren Account einsehen und aktualisieren und/oder die Korrektur, Löschung oder Sperrung Ihrer persönlichen Daten anfordern. Bitte verwenden Sie dazu die in der SAP-Datenschutzerklärung genannte E-Mail-Adresse oder [mailto:careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com).

Wenn Sie Ihr Profil über einen Zeitraum von 24 Monaten nicht angepasst haben, kann SAP per Mail eine Aktualisierung Ihrer Daten von Ihnen anfordern. Führen Sie diese in der angegebenen Frist nicht aus, wird Ihr Profil einschließlich Ihrer persönlichen Daten gelöscht.

Bitte nutzen Sie ausschließlich private E-Mail-Adressen für Anfragen. SAP wird Informationen nur an private Adressen senden.

**2\. Bewerbung**  
Sie haben auch die Möglichkeit, sich ausschließlich für eine definierte Position zu bewerben. Um diese Restriktion wirksam werden zu lassen, müssen Sie Ihre Benutzereinstellungen bei Aktivierung Ihrer Registrierung oder vor dem Absenden Ihrer Bewerbung entsprechend kennzeichnen. Indem Sie sich auf eine konkrete Stellenausschreibung bewerben, stellen Sie SAP Ihre persönlichen Daten im oben dargelegten Umfang zur Verfügung. Sie sind selbst dafür verantwortlich, dass die von Ihnen zur Verfügung gestellten persönlichen Daten korrekt sind und der Wahrheit entsprechen. Mit dem Absenden Ihrer Bewerbung erklären Sie sich damit einverstanden, dass Ihre persönlichen Daten, sofern nicht anders angegeben, gemäß den oben genannten Prinzipien für die Besetzung von Stellen verwendet werden, die Ihrem Profil entsprechen.

Sie können Ihre Bewerbung jederzeit zurückzuziehen. Nach Ende des Bewerbungsprozesses oder wenn Sie Ihre Bewerbung zurückziehen, werden Ihre Daten entsprechend den jeweils anwendbaren gesetzlichen Vorschriften gelöscht. Ihre Daten werden jedoch für einen bestimmten Zeitraum nicht gelöscht, wenn Sie Ihre im Rahmen der Bewerbung registrierten Daten freigeben. In diesem Fall gilt der in Punkt 1 beschriebene Prozess.

Bitte nutzen Sie ausschließlich private Adressen für Anfragen. SAP wird Informationen nur an private Adressen senden.

**3\. Anonyme Umfragen**  
Um ihre Prozesse stetig zu verbessern, bittet die SAP Personalverwaltung aktuelle und ehemalige Bewerber mit einem aktiven Account gelegentlich um die Teilnahme an anonymen Umfragen. Diese Umfragen werden von SAP direkt oder im Auftrag der SAP von spezialisierten Dienstleistern durchgeführt. Dienstleister erhalten für diesen Zweck lediglich Namen, E-Mail-Adressen und eine Zuordnung zu einer Organisationseinheit innerhalb der SAP. Die Umfragen und die nachfolgenden Auswertungen erfolgen vollständig anonym. Namen und E-Mail-Adressen werden nach der Kontaktaufnahme gelöscht. Es steht vollkommen im Belieben der angeschriebenen Bewerber, sich an einer solchen Umfrage zu beteiligen. Wenn Sie für Umfragen nicht kontaktiert werden möchten, wenden Sie sich bitte an die folgende E-Mail-Adresse: [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com).

Bei Fragen wenden Sie sich bitte an [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com).

**4\. Nutzung von Google Analytics**  
Diese Website benutzt Google Analytics, einen Webanalysedienst der Google Inc. ("Google") . Google Analytics verwendet sog. "Cookies ", Textdateien, die auf Ihrem Computer gespeichert werden und die eine Website die eine Analyse der Benutzung der Website. Die durch den Cookie erzeugten Informationen über Ihre Benutzung diese Website (einschließlich Ihrer IP-Adresse) erzeugten Informationen werden an einen Server von Google in den USA übertragen und dort gespeichert. Google wird diese Informationen zum Zwecke der Auswertung Ihrer Nutzung der Website, um Reports über die Websiteaktivitäten für die Websitebetreiber zusammenzustellen und um weitere Dienstleistungen im Zusammenhang mit der Websitenutzung und der Internetnutzung. Auch wird Google diese Informationen an Dritte übertragen, sofern dies gesetzlich vorgeschrieben oder soweit Dritte diese Daten im Auftrag von Google. Google wird Ihre IP-Adresse mit anderen Daten von Google zusammengeführt. Sie können die Installation der Cookies durch eine entsprechende Einstellung Ihrer Browser Software verhindern, aber bitte beachten Sie, dass Sie in diesem Fall gegebenenfalls nicht sämtliche Funktionen dieser Website vollumfänglich nutzen können.

Zusätzlich können Sie dieses Plugin verwenden: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de> Google hat die Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on entwickelt. Es bietet Website-Besucher mehr Kontrolle darüber, welche Daten von Google Analytics, gesammelt Das Add-On kommuniziert mit dem Google Analytics- JavaScript (ga.js), um anzuzeigen, dass Informationen über den Website-Besuch sollte nicht an Google Analytics gesendet werden. 

### Protection des données personnelles

SAP s’engage à traiter vos données personnelles avec la plus grande confidentialité et ce, dans le plus strict respect des lois et règlements en vigueur au sein de l’Union Européennes et dans chacun des pays où est implanté SAP. Notamment, les données personnelles sont traitées conformément aux dispositions légales afférentes à la protection des données du pays dans lequel les données sont gérées.

**1\. Inscription**

Dès votre inscription sur le portail « Careers at SAP », vous acceptez que vos données personnelles enregistrées (y compris, sans que cela ne soit exhaustif, les informations recueillies par la suite au cours des entretiens, tests ou informations de référence) soient conservées, traitées par SAP et qu’elles soient utilisées à des fins de recrutement au sein du groupe SAP.

Vous pourrez à tout moment consulter et modifier les données personnelles vous concernant.

Vous acceptez que vos données personnelles soient conservées pendant toute la durée où elles seront actives dans le système et consultées par le personnel RH autorisé des sociétés du groupe SAP dans le but de vous proposer des postes en adéquation avec votre profil. En aucun cas, vos données personnelles ne seront communiquées à des tiers n’appartenant pas au groupe SAP. Dans l’hypothèse où un ou plusieurs postes correspondraient à votre profil, le personnel RH autorisé pourra transmettre vos données personnelles au responsable du département concerné et vous contacter directement.

Si vous ne souhaitez plus recevoir de propositions et être contacté par le personnel RH autorisé, vous pourrez à tout moment modifier ou supprimer l’accès à vos données personnelles dans le système par un simple verrouillage de vos données personnelles.

La mise à jour des données personnelles dans le système reste de votre ressort. En cas d’inactivité pour une durée maximale de deux ans, SAP pourra, le cas échéant, vous adresser un e-mail vous demandant de bien vouloir actualiser vos données. En cas de non réponse de votre part dans le délai qui vous sera imparti, vos données personnelles seront supprimées.

Merci de bien vouloir n’utiliser que votre adresse & e-mail personnels. SAP ne fera parvenir les informations demandées qu’à votre adresse & e-mail personnels.

Si votre candidature ne porte que sur un poste SAP spécifique, les conditions mentionnées uniquement au point 2 ci-dessous s’appliquent.

**2\. Candidatures**

Si vous ne souhaitez soumettre qu’une seule et unique candidature pour postuler à un poste/profil SAP spécifique et afin de permettre à SAP de prendre en considération votre demande, vous devrez l’indiquer clairement lors de l’envoi de votre candidature.

A l’occasion de votre candidature à un poste/profil donné, vous acceptez que vos données personnelles enregistrées (y compris, sans que cela ne soit exhaustif, les informations recueillies par la suite au cours des entretiens, tests ou informations de référence) soient conservées, traitées par SAP et qu’elles soient utilisées dans la recherche de postes en adéquation avec votre profil.

Il vous appartient de vérifier que les données vous concernant sont correctes et exactes. A cet égard, vous pourrez à tout moment consulter et modifier vos données personnelles.

Vos données personnelles pourront être consultées par le personnel RH autorisé et les directeurs/responsables en charge du recrutement pour leurs départements/services des sociétés du groupe SAP. En conséquence, vous acceptez que vos données soient transmises au sein des sociétés du groupe SAP implantées dans le monde. Vous pourrez à tout moment annuler votre candidature.

Vos données personnelles seront supprimées dans les délais requis par les dispositions locales légales applicables à compter de la fin du traitement de votre candidature ou sur demande de votre part. Cependant, vos données personnelles ne seront pas supprimées du système si elles nous ont été communiquées dans le cadre de votre inscription sur notre portail. Dans un tel cas, les conditions mentionnées uniquement au point 1 ci-dessus s’appliqueront.

Merci de bien vouloir n’utiliser que votre adresse & e-mail personnels. SAP ne fera parvenir les informations demandées qu’à votre adresse & e-mail personnels.

**3\. Enquêtes**

Afin d’assurer l’amélioration continue de ses procédés, le département RH de SAP pourra être amené à solliciter votre participation à des enquêtes de satisfaction et ce, de manière anonyme. Ces enquêtes seront effectuées par SAP. Les résultats seront entièrement anonymes.

Pour toutes observations ou questions, vous pourrez nous les adresser à l’adresse suivante : [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)

### DECLARACIÓN DE PRIVACIDAD DE SAP: OPORTUNIDADES PROFESIONALES EN SAP

### 1\. Registro

Registrarse como usuario en el sitio web Oportunidades profesionales en SAP supone la decisión voluntaria de facilitar sus datos personales a SAP y a cualquier integrante del Grupo SAP, así como el consentimiento explícito para la recopilación, el procesamiento y la utilización de dicha información de acuerdo con las pautas que se indican a continuación.

Mediante la presente declaración, reconoce que SAP, como empresa de ámbito global, tiene un funcionamiento internacional y una administración conjunta, por lo que utiliza varios sistemas para compartir información sobre recursos humanos con el fin de disponer de un sistema de contratación unificado. SAP podrá procesar los datos personales de forma manual o automática, a través de empleados de SAP y/o de terceros a los que designe y autorice a tal efecto. SAP cuenta con políticas internas en virtud de las cuales se rige por una misma normativa de seguridad a nivel internacional dentro de la empresa para el cumplimiento de las leyes de protección de datos aplicables. En el caso de que se designe a un tercero para procesar sus datos personales en nombre de SAP, este estará obligado a mantener la confidencialidad de dicha información y observar las mismas medidas de seguridad estrictas que rigen en SAP.

SAP podrá guardar y procesar sus datos personales con el fin de facilitárselos a cualquier integrante del Grupo SAP de cualquier parte del mundo a efectos de contratación y para ponerse en contacto con usted en relación con una oportunidad laboral en SAP.

Al registrarse como usuario en el sitio web Oportunidades profesionales en SAP, SAP puede grabar su dirección IP, su nombre, apellidos, fecha de nacimiento, dirección postal, número de teléfono o dirección de correo electrónico, y utilizar cookies y otras tecnologías de Internet mencionadas en la Declaración de privacidad de SAP (<http://www.sap.com/spain/about/legal/privacy.html>) para obtener información general sobre usted.

Registrándose como usuario en el sitio web Oportunidades profesionales en SAP usted confirma de forma explícita su interés por un puesto de trabajo en SAP. Por consiguiente, también facilita de forma voluntaria sus datos personales para su uso en procesos de contratación, en concreto, para presentar su perfil para cubrir cualquier puesto vacante en SAP (incluidos aquellos a los que no haya presentado su candidatura de forma expresa) y comprobar si cumple los requisitos de dicho puesto. El proceso de registro es una opción predeterminada en el proceso de presentación de una candidatura a un puesto de trabajo. Si presenta su candidatura únicamente para un puesto de trabajo concreto, se seguirá el proceso indicado en el Apartado 2 del presente documento (Presentación de candidaturas).

Registrarse como usuario en el sitio web Oportunidades profesionales en SAP e introducir su perfil también supone aceptar que SAP pueda contactar con usted con fines de marketing para recursos humanos. Si, en un momento dado, ya no desea que se contacte con usted especialmente con fines relacionados con el marketing directo o los estudios de mercado, la empresa respetará su decisión. Escriba a la siguiente dirección de correo electrónico de contacto: [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com). Asimismo, SAP no venderá sus datos personales a terceros. En el caso de que haya un puesto de trabajo vacante en SAP que se ajuste a su perfil, SAP puede enviar sus datos a los directivos responsables dentro del Grupo SAP para su validación, así como para que se pueda contactar con usted para entrevistarle. Los datos personales se procesarán mediante bases de datos y se almacenarán en archivos personales seguros.

Usted podrá, en cualquier momento, visualizar y actualizar su cuenta, así como solicitar la corrección, la eliminación o el bloqueo de sus datos personales. Consulte la dirección de correo electrónico mencionada en la Declaración de privacidad de SAP o escriba a la siguiente “dirección de correo electrónico de contacto [mailto:careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)”.

Si no actualiza su perfil en un período de dos años, SAP podrá enviarle un correo electrónico para solicitarle que lo actualice. En el caso de que no actualice su perfil antes de la fecha límite indicada, se eliminará su perfil junto con sus datos personales.

Utilice únicamente direcciones de correo electrónico privadas para las solicitudes. SAP solo le enviará información a su dirección privada.

### 2\. Presentación de candidaturas

Asimismo, puede presentar su candidatura únicamente para un puesto de trabajo concreto. Para activar estas restricciones, debe marcar sus opciones de usuario como corresponda al activar su registro o antes de enviar su candidatura.

Al presentar su candidatura a un puesto concreto, usted facilita a SAP sus datos personales en los términos indicados anteriormente. Asume la responsabilidad de garantizar que los datos personales que facilita sean correctos y ciertos. Cuando presenta su candidatura a un puesto, acepta que sus datos personales se utilicen junto con la presentación de su candidatura para cubrir puestos vacantes que se ajusten a su perfil siguiendo los principios anteriormente mencionados, excepto que se disponga de otro modo más abajo.

Puede retirar su candidatura en cualquier momento. Sus datos se eliminarán de conformidad con lo dispuesto en la legislación aplicable una vez que concluya el proceso de selección o bien en el caso de que retire su candidatura. En cambio, si ha facilitado sus datos para el proceso de registro, estos no se eliminarán durante un período de tiempo determinado. En ese caso, se seguirá el proceso descrito en el Apartado 1.

Utilice únicamente direcciones de correo electrónico privadas para las solicitudes. SAP solo le enviará información a su dirección privada.

### 3\. Encuestas anónimas

El departamento de Recursos Humanos de SAP tiene la voluntad de mejorar constantemente sus procesos. Por ese motivo, solicitan a los candidatos a un puesto de trabajo (o personas que hayan presentado candidaturas anteriormente y tengan una cuenta activa) que participen en encuestas anónimas que realizan puntualmente. Estas encuestas puede llevarlas a cabo SAP o bien un servicio externo especializado en representación de SAP. Para tal fin, cualquier servicio externo únicamente le pedirá que facilite su nombre, su dirección de correo electrónico y una referencia a una unidad organizativa de SAP. Tanto las encuestas como los informes resultantes son totalmente anónimos. Su nombre y dirección de correo electrónico se eliminarán una vez que se haya contactado con usted por correo electrónico. Usted tiene total libertad de participar o no en dichas encuestas. Si prefiere que no se contacte con usted para la realización de encuestas, comuníquelo escribiendo a la siguiente dirección de correo electrónico: [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com).

Para cualquier consulta u observación, escriba a [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)

### 隐私声明 — Careers at SAP

### 1\. 提交

您注册成为 Careers at SAP 网站的用户，即表明您自愿向 SAP 及任何 SAP 集团的下属公司提供您的个人数据，且您明确同意 SAP 及任何 SAP 集团的下属公司依据下文所述规则收集、处理和使用该等信息。

您特此承认，为了共享人力资源信息，并使用统一的招聘系统，SAP作为一家跨国公司，采用多个系统进行联合管理和跨国运营。SAP 可以授权 SAP 员工和/或其他指定第三方手动处理或自动处理个人数据。为了遵循适用的数据保护法，SAP 制定了确保 SAP 在全球范围内执行相同安全标准的内部政策。此外，任何指定第三方代表 SAP 处理个人数据的，该等第三方均有义务对信息保密，并与SAP共同遵循同样严格的安全措施。

为了实施招聘流程和向您提供 SAP 的工作机会，SAP 可以存储和处理您的个人数据，以便 SAP 集团的任何下属公司能共享此类信息。

当您在 Careers at SAP 网站上注册用户时，SAP 可能记录您的 IP 地址、姓名、出生日期、家庭住址、电话号码或电子邮件地址，并使用 SAP 隐私声明(<http://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html>)中所述的Cookie 和其他互联网技术，收集您的一般信息。  
您注册成为 Careers at SAP 网站的用户，即表明您明确确认：您有意成为 SAP 的雇员。因此，您自愿提供您的个人数据，用于招聘目的，尤其用于将您的资料与 SAP 的所有任何空缺职位（包括但不限于您具体申请的职位）进行匹配和用于填补空缺职位之目的。注册流程属于申请流程的默认设置。如您仅申请特定的工作机会，则适用下面第二节（申请）中所述的流程。

您注册成为 Careers at SAP 网站的用户并在网站上发布您的资料，即表明您进一步同意 SAP 可以出于人力资源营销之目的与您取得联系。在特定时间内，如果您不希望再接收此类信息（尤其是与直接营销以及市场调查有关的信息），我们将尊重您的选择。请发送电子邮件至[careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)，联系我们。此外，SAP 不会将您的个人信息出售给任何第三方。如果 SAP 提供的工作机会与您的资料相匹配，则 SAP 会将您的信息转交给 SAP 集团的相关经理，以进一步确认信息和安排面试事宜。SAP 将以数据库的形式处理个人数据，并采用安全的个人文件收集数据。  
您可以随时查看和更新您的帐户和/或请求更改、删除或锁定您的个人数据。请通过 SAP 隐私声明中所述的电子邮件地址或使用以下联系方式（[careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)），与我们取得联系。

如您在两年内并未更新资料，SAP 会向您发送电子邮件，通知您更新资料。如您未在规定的截止日期之前作出更新，您的资料（包括个人数据）将会被删除。

请使用个人电子邮件地址完成相关申请。SAP 只向您的个人电子邮件地址发送信息。

### 2\. 申请

您也可以只申请某一特定的工作机会。为了激活相关限制条件，您需要在激活注册时或发送申请之前，进行相关用户设置。

在申请特定工作机会时，您需要向 SAP 提供上文规定的个人数据。您必须确保所提供的个人数据正确无误。除非下文另有规定，否则，您提交申请即表明您同意：SAP 可以按照上述规定将您的个人数据用于补充适合您的空缺职位。

您有权随时取消申请。在申请流程结束或您取消申请时，SAP 将依据适用法律删除您的数据。但是，如果您已在注册流程中发布数据，则这些数据将在一段时间内无法删除。在这种情况下，适用第一节中所述的流程。

请使用个人电子邮件地址完成相关申请。SAP 只向您的个人电子邮件地址发送信息。

### 3\. 匿名调查

一直以来，SAP 人力资源部门致力于持续改进流程。因此，他们有时会邀请申请人（和拥有活跃帐户的在先申请人）参与匿名调查。这些调查由 SAP 或专业的外部处理方代表 SAP 组织开展。出于这一目的，任何外部处理方仅会将您的姓名、电子邮件地址和介绍信息转交至 SAP 的组织单位。调查及生成的报告完全匿名。在我们通过电子邮件通知您之后，您的姓名和电子邮件地址将被删除。当然，是否参与调查完全由您自行决定。如果您不希望接收此类调查信息，请发送电子邮件至 [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)。

如有任何疑问或意见，请发送电子邮件至 [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)。

ご意見、ご質問は [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com) までお願いいたします。

### SAP プライバシー声明 – CAREERS AT SAP

### 1.註冊

在「SAP 職缺」網站註冊為使用者之後，即代表您自願將個人資料提供給 SAP 和其附屬公司，並明確同意讓 SAP 根據下述原則針對您的資料進行收集、處理和利用。

您確知 SAP 為一間全球性企業，透過多種系統進行跨國營運管理來共享人力資源以達成統一人員招募系統的目的。 SAP 得由其授權員工和/或其他授權指派的第三方，手動或自動處理您的個人資料。 SAP 的內部政策可讓 SAP 全球集團內部具有同等的資料安全標準，以符合現行的資料保護法規。 此外，若有 SAP 授權的第三方代表 SAP 處理您的個人資料，該方也應負有保密義務並遵循同等嚴謹的 SAP 資料安全措施。

您的個人資料得由 SAP 儲存、處理並與全球 SAP 集團的所有成員共享，並以招募用途為目的，作為聯絡並提供您 SAP 的工作機會之用。

當您在「SAP 職缺」網站註冊為使用者時，SAP 得記錄您的 IP 位址、名字、姓氏、生日、地址、電話號碼或電子郵件地址，並使用 SAP 隱私權聲明 (<http://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html>) 中所述之 Cookie 和其他網路技術以收集您的相關資訊。

在「SAP 職缺」網站註冊為使用者之後，即明確表示您有興趣任職於 SAP。 亦表示您自願將個人資料提供給 SAP 做為招募目的之用，尤其願意讓您的資料與任一及所有 SAP 的職缺進行配對，包括您特意應徵的職缺。 註冊程序是應徵流程中的預設過程。 若您僅單獨應徵某一項工作機會，則適用第 2 節 (應徵) 以下所述之程序。

在「SAP 職缺」網站註冊為使用者並發佈您的個人檔案，即代表您進一步同意讓 SAP 以人力資源行銷目的與您聯絡。 若在某個特定時間，您不再希望 SAP 與您連繫進行直接行銷或市場調查，我們將尊重您的選擇。 請使用下列聯絡電子郵件： [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)。 此外，SAP 不會將您的個人資料販售給第三方。 一旦

SAP 內部有與您個人檔案匹配的工作機會，SAP 得將您的資料轉呈給 SAP 集團中負責的經理，進一步驗證您的資格，以便聯絡您參與面試。 SAP 將以資料庫形式處理個人資料，並彙整於安全保障的個人檔案中。

您隨時得以檢視及更新您的帳戶，和/或要求更正、刪除或鎖住您的個人資料。 請參考 SAP 隱私權聲明中提供的電子郵件地址，或使用下列的「聯絡電子郵件 [mailto:careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)」。

若您在兩年期間內未更新個人檔案，SAP 會傳送電子郵件要求您進行更新。 若您未在指定期限內更新您的個人檔案，則包含您個人資料的個人檔案將遭到刪除。

請僅使用私人電子郵件地址進行申請， SAP 僅會將資訊寄送至您的私人信箱。

### 2\. 應徵

您同時可能單獨應徵某項限定的工作機會。 若要啟用這些限制，您必須在註冊生效或傳送申請之前，根據限制調整使用者設定。

應徵特定工作機會，即代表您將個人資料提供給 SAP 做為前述目的之用。 您有責任確保所提供的個人資料真實不虛。 提交您的工作申請，即代表您同意將個人資料依照上述原則用於進行職缺配對，除非於下另有聲明。

您隨時得以撤銷您的申請。 一旦應徵程序結束，或是您撤銷申請，您的資料將依照現行法規隨之刪除。 然而，若您因發佈個人資料以便進行註冊程序，則您的資料在特定期間將不會遭到刪除。 此種情況，適用第 1 節所述之程序。

請僅使用私人地址進行申請， SAP 僅會將資訊寄送至您的私人地址。

### **3\. 不記名調查**

SAP 人力資源部門持續追求流程改善。 因此，他們不時會邀請應徵者 (及有效帳戶的前應徵者) 參與不記名調查。 這些調查可能由 SAP 自行進行，或由代表 SAP 的外部專責處理人員進行。 為此調查目的，所有外部處理人員皆僅可取得您的姓名、電子郵件以及 SAP 內組織單位所提供的參考資料。 調查及結果報告將完全不記名。 在我們使用電子郵件與您聯絡之後，即會刪除您的姓名和電子郵件地址。 當然，是否參與調查則完全視您的個人意願。 若您不想收到調查活動的通知，請使用下列信箱告知： [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)。

若您有任何疑問或意見，請與 [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com) 聯絡。 

###  隱私權聲明 – SAP 職缺

### 1.註冊

在「SAP 職缺」網站註冊為使用者之後，即代表您自願將個人資料提供給 SAP 和其附屬公司，並明確同意讓 SAP 根據下述原則針對您的資料進行收集、處理和利用。

您確知 SAP 為一間全球性企業，透過多種系統進行跨國營運管理來共享人力資源以達成統一人員招募系統的目的。 SAP 得由其授權員工和/或其他授權指派的第三方，手動或自動處理您的個人資料。 SAP 的內部政策可讓 SAP 全球集團內部具有同等的資料安全標準，以符合現行的資料保護法規。 此外，若有 SAP 授

的第三方代表 SAP 處理您的個人資料，該方也應負有保密義務並遵循同等嚴謹的 SAP 資料安全措施。

您的個人資料得由 SAP 儲存、處理並與全球 SAP 集團的所有成員共享，並以招募用途為目的，作為聯絡並提供您 SAP 的工作機會之用。

當您在「SAP 職缺」網站註冊為使用者時，SAP 得記錄您的 IP 位址、名字、姓氏、生日、地址、電話號碼或電子郵件地址，並使用 SAP 隱私權聲明 (<http://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html>) 中所述之 Cookie 和其他網路技術以收集您的相關資訊。

在「SAP 職缺」網站註冊為使用者之後，即明確表示您有興趣任職於 SAP。 亦表示您自願將個人資料提供給 SAP 做為招募目的之用，尤其願意讓您的資料與任一及所有 SAP 的職缺進行配對，包括您特意應徵的職缺。 註冊程序是應徵流程中的預設過程。 若您僅單獨應徵某一項工作機會，則適用第 2 節 (應徵) 以下所述之程序。

在「SAP 職缺」網站註冊為使用者並發佈您的個人檔案，即代表您進一步同意讓 SAP 以人力資源行銷目的與您聯絡。 若在某個特定時間，您不再希望 SAP 與您連繫進行直接行銷或市場調查，我們將尊重您的選擇。 請使用下列聯絡電子郵件： [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)。 此外，SAP 不會將您的個人資料販售給第三方。 一旦 SAP 內部有與您個人檔案匹配的工作機會，SAP 得將您的資料轉呈給 SAP 集團中負責的經理，進一步驗證您的資格，以便聯絡您參與面試。 SAP 將以資料庫形式處理個人資料，並彙整於安全保障的個人檔案中。

您隨時得以檢視及更新您的帳戶，和/或要求更正、刪除或鎖住您的個人資料。 請參考 SAP 隱私權聲明中提供的電子郵件地址，或使用下列的「聯絡電子郵件 [mailto:careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)」。

若您在兩年期間內未更新個人檔案，SAP 會傳送電子郵件要求您進行更新。 若您未在指定期限內更新您的個人檔案，則包含您個人資料的個人檔案將遭到刪除。

請僅使用私人電子郵件地址進行申請， SAP 僅會將資訊寄送至您的私人信箱。

### 2\. 應徵

您同時可能單獨應徵某項限定的工作機會。 若要啟用這些限制，您必須在註冊生效或傳送申請之前，根據限制調整使用者設定。

應徵特定工作機會，即代表您將個人資料提供給 SAP 做為前述目的之用。 您有責任確保所提供的個人資料真實不虛。 提交您的工作申請，即代表您同意將個人資料依照上述原則用於進行職缺配對，除非於下另有聲明。

您隨時得以撤銷您的申請。 一旦應徵程序結束，或是您撤銷申請，您的資料將依照現行法規隨之刪除。 然而，若您因發佈個人資料以便進行註冊程序，則您的資料在特定期間將不會遭到刪除。 此種情況，適用第 1 節所述之程序。

請僅使用私人地址進行申請， SAP 僅會將資訊寄送至您的私人地址。

### 3\. 不記名調查

SAP 人力資源部門持續追求流程改善。 因此，他們不時會邀請應徵者 (及有效帳戶的前應徵者) 參與不記名調查。 這些調查可能由 SAP 自行進行，或由代表 SAP 的外部專責處理人員進行。 為此調查目的，所有外部處理人員皆僅可取得您的姓名、電子郵件以及 SAP 內組織單位所提供的參考資料。 調查及結果報告將完全不記名。 在我們使用電子郵件與您聯絡之後，即會刪除您的姓名和電子郵件地址。 當然，是否參與調查則完全視您的個人意願。 若您不想收到調查活動的通知，請使用下列信箱告知： [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com)。

若您有任何疑問或意見，請與 [careers@sap.com](mailto:careers@sap.com) 聯絡。 

**Back to top**
